https://help.fotki.com/privacy/

Icons and Text Icons Text Add item Remove item
Fotki
Login|Free Signup
English
more...
Home >
2. Privacy Policy >
2. Privacy Policy By accessing or using the Fotki.com site, you agree to our Privacy Policy, as outlined below. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not access or use this site. Fotki reserves the right to change the Privacy Policy from time to time. Your use of this site will be subject to the most current version of the Privacy Policy at the time of such use.
Your Personal Information
When you join Fotki, we collect your name, email address, and demographic information. On some of our pages you can order products, make requests and register to receive materials. The information collected at these pages includes: the name, address, contact and billing information, transaction, and credit card information.
The Fotki site uses cookies. Cookies are small files written on your machine that help us identify members. We use them to personalize our Web site for you.
IP Address
We analyze IP addresses for system administration purposes and to gather broad demographic information. We do not link IP addresses to your computer's User ID. When you place an order using our online checkout process we record your computer's IP address along with your order to help us identify fraudulent credit card use. We may share this information with the financial institution that issued the credit card which was used to place the order, or with law enforcement authorities if we determine, or are notified, that the use of the credit card was fraudulent.
How Do We Protect Your Information?
We have a variety of security measures implemented to maintain the safety of your personal information. Your information is only accessible by a limited number of employees who have special
rights to access our servers. All sensitive information (credit card) supplied by our users is transmitted and protected via HTTPS protocol for encrypted transfer of data. We will not store your credit card information in our database unless you explicitly instruct us to do so.
Links to Other Sites
This site contains links to other sites that may offer information, products or services that may be of interest to you. Fotki is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such sites.
Jurisdiction
The statutory body that has jurisdiction to hear any claims against the organization regarding possible unfair or deceptive practices and violations of laws or regulations governing privacy is the State of New York.
Questions or Comments
If you have any questions about this privacy policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with the Web site, you can contact Fotki via email at support@fotki.com.
Terms of Services
Our Terms of Service can be found here.
Written on 2003-09-17 18:32:29 and updated on 2006-11-28 11:32:20.
About Fotki Downloads Pricing Contact Us Customer Service File a Complaint Terms of Service Privacy Policy Choose Language
© 1998-2020 FOTKI INC or its affiliates.
